American Expeditionary Forces
Marist Archives and Special Collections
American Expeditionary Forces
2.1.1.2.3
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1320
- American Expeditionary Forces, 2.1.1.2.3
  - Margaret Wilson with American soldiers, circa 1918; 35; 3.5x5 (Box 1320)
  - Margaret Wilson with American soldier, circa 1918; 36; 3.5x5 (Box 1320)
  - Captain Donald Stone, circa 1918; 37; 3.5x5 (Box 1320)
  - Cathedral of Tours, circa 1918; 38; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1320)
  - Cathedral of Tours, circa 1918; 39; 3.5x5 (Box 1320)
  - Street lined with buildings, people lining the sidewalk, circa 1918; 40; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1320)
  - Soldier and woman in front of office building, circa 1918; 41; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1320)
  - Two soldiers standing outside café, circa 1918; 42; 3.5x4.75 (Box 1320)
  - Two men pulling cart in street, automobile in background, circa 1918; 43; 3.5x5 (Box 1320)
  - Soldier sleeping on bench next to four women, circa 1918; 44; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1320)
  - Soldiers sitting outside the Y.M.C.A “Eagle Hut”, circa 1918; 45; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1320)
  - Two soldiers and woman standing amongst trees in front of building, circa 1918; 46; 4x5 (Box 1320)
  - Soldier holding child dressed as sailor, child’s hat says “U.S.S. Long Beach”, circa 1918; 47; 3.5x4x5 (Box 1320)
  - Soldier with cane standing on sidewalk with elaborate building in background, circa 1918; 48; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1320)
  - Soldiers sitting in horse buggy with another buggy full of soldiers behind, circa 1918; 49; 4x5 (Box 1320)
  - Lowell Thomas tickling woman, soldier and old woman looking on, circa 1918; 50; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1320)
  - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas in Paris talking to two soldiers, circa 1918; 51; 4x5 (Box 1320)
  - Lowell Thomas, operating motion picture camera, records soldier kissing a woman, circa 1918; 52; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1320)
  - Two soldiers talking to a woman, Lowell Thomas operating motion picture camera, circa 1918; 53; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1320)
  - Two soldiers and two women in front of an elaborate building, circa 1918; 54; 4x5 (Box 1320)
  - Garden of an elaborate building, circa 1918; 55; 4x5 (Box 1320)
  - Two soldiers and two women in front of elaborate building, circa 1918; 56; 4x5 (Box 1320)
  - Soldiers and women in front of elaborate building, circa 1918; 57; 4x5 (Box 1320)
  - Two soldiers talking to children, circa 1918; 58; 4x5 (Box 1320)
  - Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi talking to soldiers at outdoor café, circa 1918; 59; 2.5x3.25 film (Box 1320)
  - Woman attempting to give soldier a flower in pot, circa 1918; 60; 2x3 film (Box 1320)
  Box 1321
- American Expeditionary Forces, 2.1.1.2.3
  - Soldier talking to woman with basket, circa 1918; 1; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers and civilians standing in street, circa 1918; 2; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers standing on sidewalk, children in the street, circa 1918; 3; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Two soldiers standing outside building with women and children, circa 1918; 4; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Aerial view of city and ships by docks, blimp flying in distance, circa 1918; 5; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Tree lined street, people walking down street next to river, circa 1918; 6; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Many soldiers overlooking small town, circa 1918; 7; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Aerial view of country road and river lined with houses and trees, circa 1918; 8; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldier standing among rocks [ruins?] overlooking house and fields, circa 1918; 9; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldier looking over fields, houses from a hill, circa 1918; 10; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Two soldiers pointing up a hill at soldiers standing on ruins, circa 1918; 11; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Automobile driving on street lined with trees, circa 1918; 12; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Group of soldiers sitting in field, hills in background, circa 1918; 13; 2.5x3.5 film (Box 1321)
  - Group of soldiers in field, military equipment in foreground, circa 1918; 14; 2.5x3.5 film (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers standing in front of statue, more soldiers in background, circa 1918; 15; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Spectators watching soldiers in ceremony, circa 1918; 16; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers marching through street, large crowd of spectators watching, circa 1918; 17; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers marching through street, spectators watching from sidewalk, circa 1918; 18; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers filling street in distance, spectators lining the sidewalk, circa 1918; 19; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers marching down street, children running alongside the soldiers, circa 1918; 20; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers marching down street, close-up, child marching next to soldiers, circa 1918; 21; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers marching in street, women and children watching, circa 1918; 22; 3.5x4.6 (Box 1321)
  - Close-up of American military wagon, circa 1918; 23; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers and nuns standing together in doorway, circa 1918; 24; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Two soldiers, one holding two guns, one holding a gas mask, circa 1918; 25; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers on ship, circa 1918; 26; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers on ship looking at camera, circa 1918; 27; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers on ship, circa 1918; 28; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers in automobile driving through town street, circa 1918; 29; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers sitting outside at table, eating, automobile in background, circa 1918; 30; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers helping two women fill baskets, house in background, circa 1918; 31; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers in line, going into kitchen at base, circa 1918; 32; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Overhead view of city and boats at docks, circa 1918; 33; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Ship in harbor, tree branches on bottom and left, circa 1918; 34; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers sitting on large machine, circa 1918; 35; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Troops marching past military buildings [?], circa 1918; 36; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Three soldiers in front of house in wooded area, circa 1918; 37; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers standing outside building surrounded by trees, circa 1918; 38; 3.5x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Four military men looking at camera as soldiers on horseback walk past, circa 1918; 39; 3.5x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Seven military men standing on deck of ship, circa 1918; 40; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers examining crashed airplane in field, circa 1918; 41; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Truck full of soldiers in a town, circa 1918; 42; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Two tanks angled out of trenches toward sky, circa 1918; 43; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Airplane just off ground, other airplanes on either side, circa 1918; 44; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Family and dog looking at airplane, two cows in front of airplane, circa 1918; 45; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Pilot sitting in airplane next to plane hanger, circa 1918; 46; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Pilots congregated in front of line of airplanes, man operating motion picture camera, circa 1918; 47; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Two men sitting in airplane, circa 1918; 48; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Workers standing nearby airplane, circa 1918; 49; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Men surveying front propeller on airplane, circa 1918; 50; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Workers standing next to propeller of airplane, pilot sitting on airplane, circa 1918; 51; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Airplane in cloud covered sky, circa 1918; 52; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Airplane flying in cloud covered sky, circa 1918; 53; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers standing in front of destroyed house looking at a box, circa 1918; 54; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Man standing in doorway of building, buildings on either side destroyed, circa 1918; 55; 3.5x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Brick building, half destroyed, circa 1918; 56; 3.5x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Unidentified structure in ruins, circa 1918; 57; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Unidentified structure in ruins, circa 1918; 58; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Two standing buildings among ruins, circa 1918; 59; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Building lined streets, many buildings in ruins, sidewalk filled with ruins, circa 1918; 60; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Half-destroyed buildings, street in foreground, circa 1918; 61; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Two automobiles on street next to half destroyed house, ruins in foreground, circa 1918; 62; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Men surveying ruins of large building, circa 1918; 63; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Man standing in ruins, looking into the remaining part of building, circa 1918; 64; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Street lined with ruined buildings, column falling in center, circa 1918; 65; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Man pointing to a wall partly in ruins, circa 1918; 66; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Group of men standing in ruins, looking at camera, circa 1918; 67; 4x5 film (Box 1321)
  - Officers with pistols climbing through the ruins of a building, wires hanging from above, circa 1918; 68; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Officers pointing pistols at another soldier amid ruins, circa 1918; 69; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi standing amid ruins, circa 1918; 70; 1.5x3 film (Box 1321)
  - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi standing amid ruins talking to two other men, circa 1918; 71; 2.25x3.5 film (Box 1321)
  - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi standing amid ruins with two others, looking at camera, circa 1918; 72; 2.25x3.5 film (Box 1321)
  - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi standing amid ruins looking to side, circa 1918; 73; 2.25x3.5 film (Box 1321)
  - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi standing in front of ruined house, circa 1918; 74; 2.25x3.5 film (Box 1321)
  - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas standing in front of farmhouse, circa 1918; 75; 2.25x3.5 film (Box 1321)
  - House in ruins, circa 1918; 76; 2.25x3.5 film (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers on the S.S. Leviathon, circa 1918; 77; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers on S.S. Leviathon watching boat, circa 1918; 78; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Machinery and soldiers on deck of S.S. Leviathon, circa 1918; 79; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldier standing against machinery on deck of S.S. Leviathon, circa 1918; 80; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldier using lasso on S.S. Leviathon, other soldiers looking on, circa 1918; 81; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Soldiers sitting on decks of S.S. Leviathon next to life boats, circa 1918; 82; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Place Stanislas, Lorraine, circa 1918; 83; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1321)
  - Statue of George Washington, Paris, circa 1918; 84; 5x7 (Box 1321)
  - Lowell Thomas at a monument for Waldeck Rousseau, reflection, Paris, circa 1918; 85; 5x7 (Box 1321)
  - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas in automobile outside the Hotel Regina, motion picture camera on front of car, Paris, circa 1918; 86; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Lowell Thomas with motion picture camera, and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas in automobile outside the Hotel Regina, Paris, circa 1918; 87; 4x5 (Box 1321)
  - Man and woman in horse drawn cart, circa 1918; 88; 3x5 (Box 1321)
  - Two women, man, and child in horse drawn carriage in front of ruins, circa 1918; 89; 3x5 (Box 1321)
  - Two men, two women, and child in horse drawn cart in front of ruins, circa 1918; 90; 3x5 (Box 1321)
  Box 1322
- American Expeditionary Forces, 2.1.1.2.3
  - View of church spires from window, Paris, 1917; 1; 5x7 (Box 1322)
  - Street scene, cathedral in distance, Paris, 1917; 2; 5x7 (Box 1322)
  - Street scene, tower in distance, 1917; 3; 5x7 (Box 1322)
  - Large fountain in front of ornate building, man sitting on ground in front of fountain, 1917; 4; 5x7 (Box 1322)
  - Crowd of people and automobile in front of the Hotel Cailleux, 1917; 5; 4x5 (Box 1322)
  - Le Matin, Paris, 1917; 6; 5x7 (Box 1322)
  - Five men, standing next to automobile, reading map, 1917; 7; 4x5 (Box 1322)
  - Ornate room, France [?], 1917; 8; 5x7 (Box 1322)